Indiana University President's Office records, 1962-1968 C304
Indiana University Archives
- Subject files, 1962-1968
  - Natural areas program (Box 120)
    - Proposal for the natural sciences and research station at Monroe Reservoir, 1966-1968 (Box 120)
    - 1966 (Box 120)
  - Navy league of the United States
  - Ne, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 120)
  - Neel, James Robert, 1966-1968 (Box 120)
  - Negro (Box 121)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 121)
    - Consortium for graduate studies in business for negroes, 1968 (Box 121)
    - in higher education (Box 121)
      - 1963-1968 (Box 121)
      - 1968 (Box 121)
    - in Indiana colleges, conference on, 1968 (Box 121)
    - 98 point outline about negro progress, 1968 (Box 121)
    - In higher education special report, 1968 (Box 121)
  - Nel, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 121)
  - Nelson, Mrs. Alice, 1964-1965 (Box 121)
  - Nem, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 121)
  - Neural sciences, center for (Box 121)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 121)
    - Annual report, 1966-1967 (Box 121)
  - New, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 121)
  - Newcomen society, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 121)
  - New faculty possibilities, 1965-1966 (Box 121)
  - New York City (Box 121)
    - 1962-1968, (5 folders) (Box 121)
    - University, Bowker report "Quality and Quantity in higher education", 1964-1965 (Box 121)
  - New York State (Box 121)
    - 1962-1965, (4 folders) (Box 121)
    - University, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 121)
  - New York University, New York City, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 121)
  - New York Times, 1962-1968; (6 folders) (Box 121)
  - News bureau, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 121)
  - Newsweek, 1966-1968 (Box 121)
  - Ni, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 122)
  - Nie, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 122)
  - Nigerian Project (Box 122)
    - 1966-1968, (2 folders) (Box 122)
    - Administrative review, 1963-1964; (2 folders) (Box 122)
    - Communications media resources and needs, 1965 (Box 122)
    - Eight semi-annual report, 1964; (2 folders) (Box 122)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 122)
    - Administrative review, 1963 (Box 122)
    - Miscellaneous, 1963 (Box 122)
    - Contract – A.I.D., 1962-1963 (Box 122)
  - Nixon, introduction of the Honorable Richard M. – Convocation I.U. Auditorium, October, 1965 (Box 122)
  - No, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 122)
  - Nor, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 122)
  - Norbu, Thubten, 1965-1967 (Box 122)
  - Normal college of the American gymnastic university, 1966 (Box 122)
  - Northwestern University, commencement, 1968 (Box 122)
  - Not, 1962-1968 (Box 122)
  - Nurse training (Box 122)
    - National advisory council, 1964-1966; (3 folders) (Box 122)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 122)
    - Annual report, 1967-1968 (Box 122)
    - Central league for nursing, 1962-1963 (Box 122)
    - Indiana League for nursing, 1962-1963 (Box 122)
  - Nursing education, division of, 1962-1968; (4 folders) (Box 123)
  - Nursing, school of, annual report, 1962-1967; (3 folders) (Box 123)
  - O, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 123)
  - Oc, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 123)
  - Oe, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 123)
  - Off-campus physical facilities, 1965 (Box 123)
  - Office equipment, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 123)
  - Official university guests (Box 123)
    - 1966-1968, (2 folders) (Box 123)
    - Miscellaneous bills, 1966 (Box 123)
    - Indiana Memorial Union statements, 1965-1966 (Box 123)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 123)
    - Invitation to President Johnson, 1965-1966 (Box 123)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 123)
    - Vice-president Hubert H. Humphrey, 1965 (Box 123)
    - Indiana Memorial Union statements, 1961-1964 (Box 123)
    - Miscellaneous bills, 1961-1968 (Box 123)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 123)
    - Mrs. John F. Kennedy invited to I.U. for association of college unions golden anniversary conference, 1964 (Box 123)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 123)
  - Ohio State University, Columbus, OH, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 123)
  - University of Oklahoma, Survey on motion picture equipment in research, 1966-1967 (Box 124)
  - Ol, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 124)
  - Olympic, 1965-1966 (Box 124)
  - Om, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 124)
  - Optometry (Box 124)
    - 1962-1968, (5 folders) (Box 124)
    - Annual report, 1963-1965; (2 folders) (Box 124)
  - Opperman, Leonard, 1966-1968 (Box 124)
  - Or, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 124)
  - Organization, 1966-1968 (Box 124)
  - Organization charts, University administration, 1964-1968; (5 folders) (Box 124)
  - Os, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 124)
  - Ot, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 124)
  - P, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 124)
  - Pakistan (Box 124)
    - 1962-1968, (4 folders) (Box 124)
    - A.I.D. Contract (Box 124)
      - 1966-1968 (Box 124)
      - Post-graduate medical education, 1965 (Box 124)
      - Teachers education, 1965-1966 (Box 124)
    - IBA project, 1965 (Box 124)
    - ICA contract, 1962-1963 (Box 124)
  - Pakistan (Box 125)
    - ICA contract, 1963-1964 (Box 125)
    - Teacher training, 1966-1968 (Box 125)
  - Pal, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 125)
  - Palladium item, 1962 (Box 125)
  - Par, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 125)
  - Parkhurst enrollment studies, 1964 (Box 125)
  - Pas, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 125)
  - Patents, University patent policy, 1963-1968; (4 folders) (Box 125)
  - Patten foundation (Box 125)
    - 1962-1968, (5 folders) (Box 125)
    - Committee, annual report, 1962-1964; (2 folders) (Box 125)
    - Lectures, annual report, 1965-1968; (2 folders) (Box 125)
  - Pau, 1962-1963; 1966-1968; (2 folders) (Box 125)
  - Payroll, 1964-1967 (Box 125)
  - Payroll annual report, 1967-1968 (Box 125)
  - Payroll, Personnel Action Form, 1962-1967 (Box 125)
  - Pe, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 125)
  - Peace corps (Box 125)
    - 1965-1968, (2 folders) (Box 125)
    - Contractors overseas representative in Sierra Leone, report on, 1966; (3 folders) (Box 125)
    - 1963-1966, (3 folders) (Box 125)
  - Peace corps (Box 126)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 126)
    - Sierra Leone training project, 1965-1966 (Box 126)
    - Willis P. Porter's file, 1962-1966; (3 folders) (Box 126)
  - Peat, Marwick, Mitchell and company, 1966-1968 (Box 126)
  - Pec, 1962-1963; 1965-1966; (2 folders) (Box 126)
  - Pel, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 126)
  - Penrod, Kenneth, 1965-1966; (2 folders) (Box 126)
  - Per, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 126)
  - Periodicals and miscellaneous publications, 1962-1968; (7 folders) (Box 126)
  - Quinlin, Sterling C – remarks in Chicago, 1965 (Box 126)
  - Student Personnel, Division of - Annual reports (Box 126)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 126)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 126)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 126)
    - 1966-1967 (Box 126)
    - Relations and placement, 1962-1966; (4 folders) (Box 126)
  - Personnel, bureau of relations and placement, annual report, 1963-1964 (Box 127)
  - Peru (Box 127)
    - I.U. undergraduate program in; Int. Act., 1966-1968 (Box 127)
    - Modernization of the National University of San Marco; IAC: Int. Act., 1964-1965 (Box 127)
  - Pet, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 127)
  - Petes, 1963-1964 (Box 127)
  - Ph, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 127)
  - Pharmacology, department of, annual report, 1962-1963 (Box 127)
  - Philippines (Box 127)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 127)
    - University of, 1966-1967 (Box 127)
  - Phillips Foundation, Ellis L. (Box 127)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 127)
    - Nash Winstead report, 1966 (Box 127)
    - Wentworth Conference, 1965 (Box 127)
  - Physical plant (Box 127)
    - Change orders (policies and routing procedures), 1966-1967 (Box 127)
    - Ernst and Ernst progress report, 1966 (Box 127)
    - 1962-1968, (5 folders) (Box 127)
    - Annual report, 1962-1964; (3 folders) (Box 127)
  - Physical plant (Box 128)
    - Annual report, 1964-1968; (7 folders) (Box 128)
  - Physical facilities, bureau of, studies, 1962-1965; 1967; (4 folders) (Box 128)
  - Physical science development proposal, 1964 (Box 128)
  - Physics, department of, 1963-1965; (2 folders) (Box 128)
  - Pi, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 128)
  - Pin, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 128)
  - Pitchell, Robert J. et al, "Corporate tax support of public institutions of higher education, 1966-1968 (Box 128)
  - Pittsburgh, University of (Box 128)
    - 1965-1968, (2 folders) (Box 128)
    - "A selective study with proposals for future paths", 1966 (Box 128)
    - Study, 1966 (Box 128)
  - Pl, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 128)
  - Po, 1962-1963; 1965-1966; (2 folders) (Box 128)
  - Po, 1963-1968; 3 Folders; (3 folders) (Box 129)
  - Police administration (Box 129)
    - A Five Year Program for Curriculum Development and Faculty Improvement, 1963 (Box 129)
    - General (Box 129)
      - 1963-1964 (Box 129)
      - 1964-1965 (Box 129)
      - 1965-1966 (Box 129)
      - 1966-1968 (Box 129)
  - Polish Library (Box 129)
    - Consortium, 1963 (Box 129)
    - Proposal, 1962-1963 (Box 129)
  - Political campaign, 1962-1968; 5 Folders (Box 129)
  - Pont, John, 1965 (Box 129)
  - Poo, 1962-1968; 5 Folders (Box 129)
  - Poplars, housing, private dormitories, construction, 1963-1966 (Box 129)
  - Pos, 1966-1968 (Box 129)
  - Post high school education study committee meeting minutes, 1961-1962 (Box 129)
  - Post war building, 1962-1968; 6 Folders (Box 129)
  - Pow, 1962-1968; (4 folders) (Box 129)
  - Pr, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 129)
  - Presidency search committee, 1960-1961 (Box 129)
  - President's house, 1965-1968; (2 folders) (Box 129)
  - President's office (Box 129)
    - Items removed from files at Dr. Stahr's request, 1968 (Box 129)
    - 1962-1968, 5 Folders (Box 129)
    - Reports, budgets, etc., 1966-1968 (Box 129)
  - President's office (Box 130)
    - Personnel (Box 130)
      - Enterline, Ethel M., 1965-1968 (Box 130)
      - Ewers, Joseph R., 1965-1968 (Box 130)
      - Fletcher, Nancy K., 1966-1968 (Box 130)
      - Heile, Patricia, 1968-1969 (Box 130)
      - Langer, Gislind E.I., 1968 (Box 130)
      - Percifield, Jeanene, 1968 (Box 130)
      - Rohrbacher, Margaret, 1966-1967 (Box 130)
      - Scarola, Jane Clay, 1966-1968 (Box 130)
      - Small, Judith, K., 1965-1966 (Box 130)
      - Stahr, Elvis J., 1962 (Box 130)
      - Thickstun, Bonnie J., 1965-1969 (Box 130)
      - Zuck, Joyce Ann, 1968 (Box 130)
    - Stores inventory requisition, 1965 (Box 130)
    - Motor vehicle charges, 1962-1965 (Box 130)
    - Printing and duplicating charges, 1965-1966 (Box 130)
    - Statement of accounts, 1966-1968; (2 folders) (Box 130)
    - Telegraph charges, 1965-1968; (2 folders) (Box 130)
    - Telephone charges, 1962-1966 (Box 130)
    - Travel charges, 1964-1966 (Box 130)
    - Xerox charges, 1966 (Box 130)
    - Reports, budgets, etc., 1964-1966; (2 folders) (Box 130)
    - Payroll (Box 130)
      - Misc. – Idle, 1956-1965 (Box 130)
      - Hourly employees and some misc., 1963-1966 (Box 130)
    - Monthly statements, 1962-1963 (Box 130)
    - Reports, budgets, etc., 1957-1963 (Box 130)
    - Annual report, 1961-1968 (Box 130)
    - Selection of, 1960-1962 (Box 130)
    - Annual report (Box 130)
      - for preceding fiscal year, 1963-1968; (4 folders) (Box 130)
      - correspondence, etc., 1966-1967 (Box 130)
      - information, 1964-1967; (2 folders) (Box 130)
      - mailing list, 1966-1968 (Box 130)
  - President's office (Box 131)
    - Annual report (Box 131)
      - To the governor, 1968 (Box 131)
      - Mailing list, 1953-1966; (3 folders) (Box 131)
  - Press (Box 131)
    - Miscellaneous articles and correspondence with newsmen, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 131)
    - Lafayette Journal-Courier, Frank Arganbright's articles on education in Indiana, 1963 (Box 131)
  - Pri, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 131)
  - Printing plant (Box 131)
    - 1963-1968, (5 folders) (Box 131)
    - Annual report, 1962-1964; (2 folders) (Box 131)
    - Balance sheets, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 131)
  - Psychological clinic (Box 131)
    - Post-graduate training program in clinical psychology, annual report, 1962-1968; (6 folders) (Box 131)
  - Psychology, department of, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 131)
  - Pu, 1962-1968; (6 folders) (Box 131)
  - Public discussion, bureau of, annual report, 1963-1968; (3 folders) (Box 131)
  - Publications, 1964-1968; (3 folders) (Box 131)
  - Purchasing, 1966-1968; (6 folders) (Box 132)
  - Purdue University, West Lafayette, 1962-1970; (7 folders) (Box 132)
  - Putman, Frank W., 1964-1965 (Box 132)
  - Q, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 132)
  - R, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 132)
  - Radio and television (Box 132)
    - Dedication, 1963 (Box 132)
    - Channel 30, 1966 (Box 132)
    - 1963-1968, (5 folders) (Box 132)
    - Application for grant for construction of ETV facilities, WTIU, channel 30, 1966-1968 (Box 132)
    - Application to FCC for ITFS, 1968 (Box 132)
  - Radio and television (Box 133)
    - 1962-1965, (2 folders) (Box 133)
    - Indianapolis, 1962-1963 (Box 133)
    - New building, 1963 (Box 133)
    - Stations, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 133)
  - Raf, 1965-1966 (Box 133)
  - Ran, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 133)
  - Rat, 1962-1966; (4 folders) (Box 133)
  - Re, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 133)
  - Real estate (Box 133)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 133)
    - West Yellowstone, Montana, 1966-1968 (Box 133)
    - Monroe County, Home Builders Association, 1963-1968; (4 folders) (Box 133)
    - Controversial, 1964-1965 (Box 133)
    - Department of mental health, surplus land adjacent to Indiana Purdue regional campus, 1964 (Box 133)
    - Controversial matters, 1962-1965 (Box 133)
    - Controversial, Fulkerson-Leonard property, 1965 (Box 133)
    - 1964-1968, (4 folders) (Box 133)
    - Hillcrest Apartments, 1965-1967 (Box 133)
    - Annual report (Box 133)
      - 1963-1964 (Box 133)
      - 1964-1965 (Box 133)
      - 1967-1968 (Box 133)
  - Rebhun, Herbert F., correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 133)
  - Records and admissions (Box 133)
    - 1964-1968, (2 folders) (Box 133)
    - Annual report (Box 133)
      - 1962-1963 (Box 133)
      - 1963-1964 (Box 133)
      - 1965-1966 (Box 133)
      - 1966-1967 (Box 133)
  - Recreation and park administration, annual report (Box 133)
    - 1966-1967 (Box 133)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 133)
  - Red Mass of the St. Thomas More Society, 1965 (Box 133)
  - Ree, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 134)
  - Regional campuses (Box 134)
    - Credit class sections report, 1966-1967 (Box 134)
    - Annual report (Box 134)
      - 1966-1968, (2 folders) (Box 134)
      - Eastern (Earlham), 1965-1968; (2 folders) (Box 134)
      - Fort Wayne, 1963-1968; (3 folders) (Box 134)
      - Indianapolis (Box 134)
        - 1963-1968, (4 folders) (Box 134)
        - Plan, undated (Box 134)
      - Kokomo (Box 134)
        - 1963-1968, (4 folders) (Box 134)
        - Dedication, 1965 (Box 134)
      - Libraries, 1965-1967; (2 folders) (Box 134)
      - Master plan (Box 134)
        - First revision, 1966 (Box 134)
        - 1966 (Box 134)
      - Northwest, 1963-1968; (3 folders) (Box 134)
      - Purdue Regional Campuses, Status Reports of Currently Existing Credit Offerings(includes reports from IUPUI and IUPFW), 1966 (Box 134)
      - South Bend, 1963-1971; (4 folders) (Box 134)
      - Southeast, 1963-1968; (4 folders) (Box 134)
  - Registration, Freshman arrival, 1964-1966 (Box 134)
  - Register, 1962-1967; (4 folders) (Box 134)
  - Rei, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 134)
  - Rel, 1962-1963 (Box 134)
  - Religion, 1962-1968; (3 folders) (Box 134)
  - Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute of Connecticut, 1962-1965 (Box 134)
  - Representation funds, 1967 (Box 134)
  - Requisitions, Archives, 1965-1967; (2 folders) (Box 134)
  - Research (Box 134)
    - 1963-1968, (3 folders) (Box 134)
    - Heart research project site and grant renewal application, 1962 (Box 134)
  - Research agencies in university communities, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 134)
  - Research and advanced studies, graduate school, 1964-1968; (2 folders) (Box 134)
  - Research and advanced studies annual report, 1965-1968; (3 folders) (Box 135)
  - Research, Bureau of institutional (Box 135)
    - University governance: Current changes and an annotated bibliography, undated (Box 135)
    - Unit cost analysis procedure Indiana University, 1964 (Box 135)
    - Organization chart, 1963-1964 (Box 135)
    - 1962-1968, (5 folders) (Box 135)
  - Research center in anthropology, folklore, and linguistics (Box 135)
    - General, 1962-1968; (4 folders) (Box 135)
    - Annual report (Box 135)
      - 1962-1963 (Box 135)
      - 1963-1964 (Box 135)
      - 1964-1965 (Box 135)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 135)
    - Annual report, 1964-1965 (Box 135)
    - Appointments, 1964-1965 (Box 135)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 135)
  - Research center in the atmospheric sciences, proposed, 1965 (Box 135)
  - Research center for marine sciences, proposed, 1963 (Box 135)
  - Research center for water resources, 1962-1966; (5 folders) (Box 135)
  - Research committee, Indiana University (Box 136)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 136)
    - School science coordinator's advisory committee, 1968 (Box 136)
    - Minutes, 1967-1968 (Box 136)
    - Agenda, 1968 (Box 136)
    - Minutes, 1968 (Box 136)
    - Information, 1968 (Box 136)
    - Minutes, June – July 1968 (Box 136)
    - 1968 (Box 136)
    - Minutes, March – May, 1968 (Box 136)
    - January – February 1968 (Box 136)
    - Minutes, January – February 1968 (Box 136)
    - Minutes, July – December 1967 (Box 136)
    - October 1967 (Box 136)
    - July – August 1967 (Box 136)
    - April – May 1968 (Box 136)
    - Minutes, March - June 1967 (Box 136)
  - Research committee, Indiana University (Box 137)
    - Minutes, January – February 1967 (Box 137)
    - Minutes, November – December 1966 (Box 137)
    - Minutes, July – October 1966 (Box 137)
    - Minutes, June – July 1966 (Box 137)
    - Minutes, January – June 1966 (Box 137)
    - Minutes, July 1964 – June 1965 (Box 137)
    - 1965 (Box 137)
    - Minutes, July 1963 – June 1964 (Box 137)
    - 2nd semester, 1962-1963 (Box 137)
  - Research committee, Indiana University (Box 138)
    - 1st semester, 1962-1963 (Box 138)
    - Applications, 1962-1963 (Box 138)
    - July 1962 – June 1963 (Box 138)
    - Minutes, 1962-1963 (Box 138)
  - Research computing center (Box 138)
    - 1962-1968, (5 folders) (Box 138)
    - Annual report, 1962-1963 (Box 138)
  - Research contracts, Self-instructional elementary French course, 1965 (Box 138)
  - Research, Heart research project site visit and grant renewal application for 1968-1975, 1965 (Box 138)
  - Research grants, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 138)
  - Research miscellaneous, 1964-1965 (Box 138)
  - Research proposals, 1965-1967; (2 folders) (Box 138)
  - Research questionnaires, 1963-1968; (4 folders) (Box 138)
  - Research, Stanford Institute's "An exploratory study of the structure and dynamics of the R & D industry", 1964 (Box 139)
  - Reserve officers training (Box 139)
    - 1965-1968, (2 folders) (Box 139)
    - Commencement, 1966 (Box 139)
  - Ri, 1966-1968 (Box 139)
  - Riley hospital (Box 139)
    - Cheer guild, 1964-1967; (2 folders) (Box 139)
    - Groundbreaking, 1967 (Box 139)
  - ROTC Act, committee to consider implications for I.U., 1964-1965 (Box 139)
  - Reserve officers training corps (Box 139)
    - 1964-1965, (2 folders) (Box 139)
    - Report of the special committee to study the ROTC vitalization act of 1964 (Box 139)
    - HR-9124 – HR-8130, testimony by president Stahr, 1963-1965 (Box 139)
    - 1962-1964, (2 folders) (Box 139)
    - Adjutant general's officer career class, Ft. Benjamin Harrison, March – April, 1963 (Box 139)
    - 1962-1968, (5 folders) (Box 139)
  - Residency (Box 139)
    - Folder, 1966 (Box 139)
    - Questions, 1st semester, Lloyd Keisler, 1967-1968 (Box 139)
    - Questions, 2nd semester, 1967-1968 (Box 139)
  - Residential colleges, 1966-1968; (2 folders) (Box 139)
  - Residential labor program, 1962-1966; (5 folders) (Box 139)
  - Resources for the future, 1963-1968; (2 folders) (Box 140)
  - Retirement and group insurance annual report, 1967-1968 (Box 140)
  - Rhodes scholarship and Indiana committee selection (Box 140)
    - 1962-1968 (Box 140)
    - Reunion, 1965 (Box 140)
  - Ri, 1962-1966; (4 folders) (Box 140)
  - Rick, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 140)
  - Ril, 1963-1968; (3 folders) (Box 140)
  - Riley hospital cheer guild, 1962-1964; 1966-1968; (3 folders) (Box 140)
  - Riley, Stewart, 1962-1965; (3 folders) (Box 140)
  - Ris, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 140)
  - Ro, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 140)
  - Robbins report, Committee on higher education (British), 1961-1963 (Box 140)
  - Robi, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 140)
  - Rockefeller foundation, 1963-1968; (5 folders) (Box 140)
  - Rod, 1962-1964; 1966-1968; (3 folders) (Box 140)
  - Rog, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 140)
  - Rol, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 140)
  - Ros, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 140)
  - Rose Polytechnic Institute centennial, 1965 (Box 140)
  - Ross, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 140)
  - Rotary Club, Evansville, 1965 (Box 140)
  - Rou, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 141)
  - Ru, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 141)
  - Run, 1962-1964; (2 folders) (Box 141)
  - Russian and East European studies (Box 141)
    - 1962-1968, (4 folders) (Box 141)
    - Annual report, 1962-1963 (Box 141)
  - Ry, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 141)
  - S, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 141)
  - Sabbatical leaves of absence (Box 141)
    - 1962-1968, (5 folders) (Box 141)
    - Annual report, 1963-1968; (4 folders) (Box 141)
  - Safety (Box 141)
    - 1963-1968, (4 folders) (Box 141)
    - Training manual, 1964 (Box 141)
    - Seventh and Jordan intersection, 1965 (Box 141)
    - Big Ten policies re campus police, 1964 (Box 141)
    - Annual report, 1962-1964; (2 folders) (Box 141)
    - Miscellaneous, 1962-1963 (Box 141)
    - Parking, 1956-1968; (5 folders) (Box 141)
  - Safety (Box 142)
    - Parking (Box 142)
      - Maps and reports, 1963 (Box 142)
      - 1962-1965, (4 folders) (Box 142)
  - Saint – Sainte – St., 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 142)
  - Sal, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 142)
  - Salzburg seminar, 1965-1968; (2 folders) (Box 142)
  - San, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 142)
  - Sar, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 142)
  - Sc, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 142)
  - Scha, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 142)
  - Sche, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 142)
  - Schedule of classes, 1964-1965; (2 folders) (Box 142)
  - Schi, 1962-1968; (4 folders) (Box 142)
  - Schm, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 142)
  - Schn, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 142)
  - Scho, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 142)
  - Scholarships and financial aids, office of, annual report, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 142)
  - Scholarships (Box 143)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 143)
    - Kent Cooper, 1966-1968 (Box 143)
    - To individuals by outside agencies, 1966-1968 (Box 143)
    - Fulbright awards, 1966-1968 (Box 143)
    - General motors, 1966-1968 (Box 143)
    - National merit scholarship corporation, 1966-1968 (Box 143)
    - Resident (residence) scholarships, 1951-1968 (Box 143)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 143)
    - Kent Cooper, 1965-1966 (Box 143)
    - Dow Chemical, 1965-1966 (Box 143)
    - Fulbright awards, 1965-1966 (Box 143)
    - General motors, 1965-1966 (Box 143)
    - Japanese (Mombusho) scholarship program, 1965-1966 (Box 143)
    - Arthur R. Metz Foundation, 1965 (Box 143)
    - National merit scholarship corporation, 1965-1966 (Box 143)
    - To individuals by outside agencies, 1965 (Box 143)
    - Radio corporation America, 1965-1966 (Box 143)
    - Rhodes, Indiana committee selection, 1965 (Box 143)
    - United States steel foundation, 1965 (Box 143)
    - Western gold association (Evans scholarship program), 1965-1966 (Box 143)
    - Dow Chemical company, 1964-1965 (Box 143)
    - Freshman scholarship program, 1964 (Box 143)
    - Fulbright awards, 1965 (Box 143)
    - General motors, 1965 (Box 143)
    - Indiana Bar Association, 1965 (Box 143)
    - Marshall award, 1965 (Box 143)
    - National defense education act, 1965 (Box 143)
    - National merit scholarship corporation, 1964-1965 (Box 143)